[
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{2}{4}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{2}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{81}{27}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{9}{6}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{2}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{12}{16}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{4}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{18}{24}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{4}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{20}{25}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{4}{5}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{15}{35}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{7}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{14}{49}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{2}{7}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{32}{40}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{4}{5}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{45}{60}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{4}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{50}{100}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{2}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{63}{81}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{7}{9}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{27}{36}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{4}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{40}{60}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{2}{3}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{18}{27}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{2}{3}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{56}{64}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{7}{8}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{81}{90}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{9}{10}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{100}{120}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{5}{6}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{48}{64}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{4}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Skróć ułamek $$\\frac{72}{96}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{4}"
    }
]
